

Front End Developer

- +20 1017504320
- waledkama2510@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/waledkamal/
- https://github.com/WaledKamal

OBJECTIVE



SKILLS

HTML5

Node.js

CSS/CSS3

Javascript

GIT/Github

AWS Docker

APIs

PHP / WordPress

React.js / Redux React Native

UI/UX Knowlodge

FTP / Hosting



I dealt with developing programming interfaces for more than 3 years. That started with HTML CSS JavaScript and its famous library React. There is no problem with it being a framework as some call it. The most important thing is that I have been doing it well for more than 3 years and dealt with PHP and it continued I have worked for more than two years in WordPress and dealing with themes

I currently reside in Luxor, Egypt

EXPERIENCE

Mostafa Mahmoud Library

Sep 2020 – Present

Luxor, Egypt

Founder and Software Developer

Creating App for Library using (React Native, Firebase)

- Creating UI / UX
- Firebase Configuration

Live Perview

Mostaql

August 2017 - Present

(Remotly Freelancer)

WordPress Developer

- Create websites with WordPress & Mobile Apps
- Install Themes & Plugins
- **Build Pages Elementor Portofilio**

Diamond ART DK

August 2019 - 2021

Jan 2018 - Jul 2017

Give, Denmark

Web Designer / Front End Developer

Creating wireframe, Designing website, UI/UX Designs, front end development (HTML, CSS), Designing banners, Working with the Danish Marketing Team to plan and implement designs and digital marketing potential.

Digital Creativity Foundation

Saudi Arabia (Internship)

Juinor Java Developer

- Handling the basics of the Java
- Data Structure (Java)
- Algorithms
- Design Patterns MVC Pattern

- FOCUSED ON (o)



- UI/UX Design
- HTML5/CSS3/Sass
- Web Design
- Wireframing/Prototype

LANGUAGES



- Arabic
- 🛡 English
- French

PERSONAL

Date of birth 25/10/2001

Merital status

Single

Driving License

No

INTERESTED IN®

- Photography
- Travelling
- Reading

PORTFOLIO



GitHub Here

EDUCATION



2020 – 2024 Luxor University (Egypt)

Bachelor of Tourism and Pharaonic Studies